American Association of University Women, Waco Branch records, Inclusive: 1923-2002, undated, Bulk: 1926-1997, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
American Association of University Women, Waco Branch records
Inclusive: 1923-2002, undated, Bulk: 1926-1997, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
232
American Association of University Women, Waco Branch.
17 document boxes 4 OVZ boxes
The American Association of University Women Waco Branch records contain correspondence, membership listings, yearbooks, by-laws, and publications for local, state, and national levels. Branch projects and scrapbooks are also included.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
The Association of Collegiate Alumnae was founded in Boston, Massachusetts, in 1882 as a group to develop higher education for women and maintain high standards in institutions serving women. In 1921, the ACA merged with the Southern Association of College Women and formed the American Association of University Women.
In 1923, AAUW worked with several institutions in Texas, including Baylor University, to recognize them as approved schools. The organization approved schools based on women’s rank and representation in the faculty, housing facilities, educational opportunities, membership among the Board of Trustees (Regents), and other criteria. In 1926, Waco, along with Amarillo, Austin, Commerce, Dallas, El Paso, Fort Worth, Georgetown, Lubbock, and San Antonio, became charter branches of the AAUW Texas Division. The Waco Branch membership was made up of women in Bosque, Hill, Coryell, Falls, Limestone, and McLennan counties.
For most of the 20th Century, the Waco Branch operated in accordance with state and national guidelines promoting education and equity for women. The Waco Branch hosted the Biennial State Conference in 1930, 1945, and 1975, usually at Baylor University, which held an institutional membership. The branch consistently donated to the national AAUW Educational Foundation and provided several scholarships to young women in their senior year of undergraduate study.
Declining numbers of faculty and staff participants caused Baylor University to discontinue institutional affiliation with the national AAUW in 1997. The Waco Branch remained active until 2001, when rising dues costs and membership decline caused the branch to disband.
Scope and Content
The American Association of University Women (AAUW), Waco Branch records are representative of early women’s history at Baylor University and women’s history in the greater Waco area throughout the 20th century. This may be because members throughout branch history were either employed by Baylor or were alumnae of the university. Membership was open to alumnae of any college or university in the area.
The Administrative series establishes the group as a working body for the advancement of women through education and equity. Charters, by-laws, membership information, and treasury reports are present. Several conventions are also represented, including audiocassettes of speeches from the 1979 national convention in Albuquerque, New Mexico. Additional related materials can be found in the Hamilton House records. Hamilton House was used as a regular meeting place for women’s groups in the Waco area, including AAUW.
The Correspondence series includes general letters to and from all levels of the organizations. Of specific note might be the 1923 letters between Baylor University President, Samuel Palmer Brooks, and the national AAUW organization. This interaction was key in establishing a named position, Dean of Women, and adding a female presence to the Baylor Board of Regents.
The Projects and Publications series includes newsletters from the local, state, and national levels of the organization. The newsletters, journals, research reports, and magazines will be beneficial to those researching women’s issues, how they were supported or rejected by the organization, and how they changed over time. The series also includes directories, yearbooks, and membership handbooks for the Waco Branch. A fundraising cookbook and history of Waco’s first female doctor, Hallie Earle, are also included. Projects promoted and hosted by the Waco Branch are also represented.
The Photographs and Scrapbooks series is telling of the organization from start to finish. The earliest scrapbook holds the most information regarding the beginnings of the Waco Branch. Newsletters, correspondence, and other materials are present. Later scrapbooks include similar items, but also begin to incorporate photographs. This series is the most comprehensive of Branch activities.
Arrangement
There was no previous arrangement for the collection. There are now four series, Series I: Administrative, Series II: Correspondence, Series III: Projects and Publications, and Series IV: Photographs and Scrapbooks.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 232. Acquired 0-00-00
Related Resources
Items in related collections
[Waco] Hamilton House records, Inclusive: 1864-2006, undated, Bulk: 1953-2003, undated
BU Records: Dean of Women (Lily Russell), Inclusive: 1922-1969, undated, Bulk: 1935-1945
Related references
“Our History.” American Association of University Women. Accessed 24 November 2020.
“AAUW.” Texas Woman’s University Woman’s Collection. Accessed 24 November 20219.
Index Terms
Subjects (Organizations)
American Association of University Women. Waco Branch.; Baylor University -- Women -- History.
Subjects
Women -- Societies and clubs -- History.; Women -- Texas -- Waco -- Societies and clubs.; Women college graduates -- Societies and clubs -- History.
Genres
By-laws.; Correspondence.; Membership lists.; Minutes (Records); Newsletters.; Photographs.; Scrapbooks.; Yearbooks.
- Administrative, 1923-2001, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  The Administrative Series, dated 1923-2002, includes minutes, charters, by-laws, convention bid proposals, and other general materials. Also included are membership rosters, treasurer’s reports, committee reports, handbooks, convention materials, scholarship materials, and branch award certificates. The series is in chronological order and in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Cassette tape
  - General, 1923, 1928-1932 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Charter & By-Laws, 1927-1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Branch Presidents, Texas Division, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General, 1936-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - State & Local Resolutions, 1936-1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Speakers, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - General, 1940-1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General, 1944-1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Committees: International Relations Study Group, 1945-1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Membership Rosters, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Degrees, Experience & Publications of Women Faculty Members at Baylor University, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - General, 1950-1958, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Waco Branch President’s Report, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Membership Rosters, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Account Books, 1954-1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Membership & Treasurer’s Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Membership & Treasurer’s Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - General Director’s Letter [Leadership Newsletter], 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Membership & Treasurer’s Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Membership & Treasurer’s Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General, 1965-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Membership & Treasurer’s Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Membership & Treasurer’s Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Membership & Treasurer’s Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Membership & Treasurer’s Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Membership, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - State Convention in Abilene, Texas Arrangements Committee, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Membership, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Membership, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Membership, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Legal Rights of Texas Women [Handbook], 1974, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - General, 1974-1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Waco Branch By-Laws, 1974-1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Texas State Convention, Baylor University, Waco, Texas (1 of 4), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - State Convention, Baylor University, Waco, Texas (2 of 4), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - State Convention, Baylor University, Waco, Texas (3 of 4), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - State Convention, Baylor University, Waco, Texas (4 of 4)., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Waco Branch By-Laws, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Waco Branch By-Laws, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Southwest Central Region Conference Hot Springs, Arkansas, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Texas Division Summer Conference, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Waco Branch By-Laws, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Texas Division Convention & State Board of Directors, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Charter & By-Laws, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - National Convention, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Convention, Albuquerque, New Mexico: ERA Keynotes, 1979 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - National Convention, Albuquerque, New Mexico: Families Facing Change, Earth’s Resources and Human Needs, 1979 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - National Convention, Albuquerque, New Mexico: Families and Social Change, 1979 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - National Convention, Albuquerque, New Mexico: Abuse: Many Meanings, Many Responses; Arts and the Learning Process, 1979 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - National Convention, Albuquerque, New Mexico: President’s Report; The Sterling and Styrofoam, 1979 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - National Convention, Albuquerque, New Mexico: In Development; Financial Planning, A Life Cycle Approach, 1979 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - National Convention, Albuquerque, New Mexico: What’s Ahead for Women; Convention Action, 1979 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - National Convention, Albuquerque, New Mexico: How to Conduct Your Job Search, 1979 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - National Convention, Albuquerque, New Mexico: Educational Foundation Night, 1979 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - State Division Handbook, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Waco Branch By-Laws, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Wedemeyer-Malone Scholarship Background Information, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - National “Centennial” Convention, Boston, Massachusetts, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Texas State Convention, Irving, Texas, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Waco Branch By-Laws, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Allen-Wildish Scholarship Applicants & Recipients, 1981-2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Wedemeyer-Malone Scholarship Application Forms, circa 1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Wedemeyer-Malone Scholarship Applicants and Recipients, 1982-1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Waco Branch By-Laws, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Minutes (General), 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Committees: Educational Foundation, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Financial Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Minutes (General), 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Meetings, 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Committees: Legal Advocacy Fund, 1990-1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Committees: Educational Foundation, Chair Handbook, circa 1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising & Branch Giving, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - By-Laws of Waco, Texas Branch, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Waco Branch By-Laws, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Minutes (Board), 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - General, 1992-1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Allen-Wildish Scholarship Fund Background Information, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - National Charter & By-Laws, 1992-1999 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Committees: Educational Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Texas Communication Handbook, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Financial Reports, 1994-2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Committees: Educational Foundation: Resource Tools, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - State Convention, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - President’s Handbook, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Committees: Yearbook Ad Solicitation, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 5- Star Branch Award Application, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Committees: Public Policy, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Membership Rosters, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Committees: Educational Foundation, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Certificates [Branch Awards], 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Minutes (Board), 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Branch Officers, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - President’s Leadership Conference Notebook, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Bid for 2002 State Convention, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Committee: Legal Advocacy Funds, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Committees: Internet, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - International Federation of University Women, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Committees: Educational Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 5-Star Branch Award Application, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Minutes (General), 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - President’s Handbook, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Meetings, 1997-2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Public Policy Program & Voter Education Campaign, 1997-2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Texas Central District Meeting, Georgetown, Texas, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - State Convention, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - General, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - General, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - National Convention, Austin, Texas, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Scholarship Transfer to Baylor, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Scholarship Recipients List, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Guidelines for Discontinuing Branch, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Scholarship Background Information, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Blank Letterhead, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Constitution & By-Laws, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Committees: Nominating, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Allen-Wildish Scholarship Letters & Application Forms, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1923-2001; 2
  The Correspondence Series, dated 1923-2001, includes mostly general correspondence between officers and state or national representatives as well as local members discussing branch matters. Letters between Samuel Palmer Brooks and AAUW discuss establishing a solid female presence on the Board of Regents and an official Dean of Women. The series is in chronological order and in good condition.
  - General, 1923-1924 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - General, 1925-1929 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - General, 1930-1936 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - General, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - General, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - General, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - To Mrs. James Leo (Grace) Garrett, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - General, 1941 January-March (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - General, 1941 March-April (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - General, 1941 May-December (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - General, 1942-1944 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - General, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - General, 1947 January-April (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - General, 1947 May-December (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - General, 1948-1956 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - To/From Virginia Crump, 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - From Betty Coley, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - From Mickey Ferguson, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - From Miss Sue Margaret Hughes, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - General, 1992-2001 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Projects and Publications, 1923-2002; 3
  The Projects and Publications series is dated 1923-2001. Local, state, and national news and activities are documented in brochures, newsletters, magazines, and journals from each level. Yearbooks and directories provide input into membership through time, while handbooks show the changing needs of the group. Journals and newsletters provide contemporary insight into women’s issues, several of which are addressed for many years. Local projects are represented in this series, many aimed at the education, needs, and promotion of women as defined by the national AAUW. The series is in good condition and arranged in chronological order.
  - Brochures, 1923-1937 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fellowship Fund, 1924-1938 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Membership & Eligibility, 1925-1940 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - National Convention Programs, 1927-1929, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Sectional Convention Programs, 1928, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Fellowship and Fellows, 1935-1941 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Austin Branch Yearbook, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Kansas Division Bulletin [Newsletters], 1940 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1941-1963 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Journal of the American Association of University Women, 1947-1948, 1952-1954 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - International Relations Study Group Yearbooks, 1948-1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Art Study Group Yearbooks, 1949-1956 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Brochures, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - International Federation of University Women Newsletters, 1952-1954, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Art Study Group Yearbooks, 1953-1956, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Journal of the American Association of University Women, 1955-1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Branch Yearbooks, 1958-1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Literature Study Group, 1960-1961, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Trends Group Yearbooks, 1965-1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - The University Woman [State Newsletters], 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - The University Woman [State Newsletters], 1966-1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Selected Topics Group Yearbooks, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - General Director’s Letter [Leadership Newsletter], 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - General Director’s Letter [Leadership Newsletter], 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Drama Study Group, 1969-1970, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Branch Yearbook, 1970-1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - National Convention Program, Dallas, Texas, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Corporate Delegates Luncheon, 1971 June (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - AAUW Journal, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Waco Branch Bulletin [Newsletter], 1972-1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - AAUW Journal, 1975-1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Branch Yearbooks, 1975-1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - State Division Leadership Handbook, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Branch Leadership Handbook, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Women Together Action [State Leadership Newsletter], 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The University Woman [State Newsletter], 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Texas Division Directory, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - New Member Handbook, 1977, 1987, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - “But We Will Persist” A Comparative Research Report on the Status of Women in Academics, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - State Division Handbook, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Woman [National Magazine], 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Waco Branch Bulletin [Newsletter], 1979-1984 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - The University Woman [State Newsletter], 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Projects & Publications, Graduate Woman [National Magazine], 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Leader In Action [National Leadership Newsletter], 1982-1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - The University Woman [State Newsletter], 1981-1985 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Woman [National Magazine], 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Waco Branch Bulletin [Newsletters], 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Woman [National Magazine], 1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - General Newsletters, 1985-1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Teen Pregnancy, 1986-1993 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Education Foundation Pamphlets, 1986-1996 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Educational Foundation: Names Honored Booklets, 1988-1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Trend Group Yearbook, 1988-2001 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Branch Yearbooks, 1988-2001 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - AAUW Education Foundation, Eleanor Roosevelt Teacher Fellowship Program, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - The Bridge [Branch Newsletters], 1988-1995 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Historic Principles, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Educational Foundation: Eleanor Roosevelt Fund for Women & Girls, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - “A Woman for All Ages”, Dr. Hallie Earle Tribute by Jessie Lee Janes, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising Cookbook, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Waco Branch Yearbooks, 1990, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - The University Woman [State Newsletter], 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Outlook [National Magazine], 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - The Bridge [Newsletters], 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Expanding Your Horizons Math & Science Conference for Young Women, 1992, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Sexual Harassment, circa 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Scholarships, 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Girls Can! Community Coalitions Project, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - College/ University Directory, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Educational Foundation, Branching Out [Newsletter], 1994-2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Leader In Action [National Leadership Newsletter], 1994-2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Membership Applications & Brochures, circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - T-Shirt Sales, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Symphony Fund, 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - IFUW News [International Federation of University Women Newsletter], 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - The Bridge [Branch Newsletter], 1995-2001 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Educational Foundation: “Girls in the Middle”: Video Guide & Research Report Working to Succeed in School, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - National Women’s History Project, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Adelante! [Diversity Outreach], 1996 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Central Texas Regional Science Fair Certificates, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Heart of Texas Regional History Fair Special Award, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The University Woman Texas! [State Newsletter], 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Austin Branch Yearbook, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Outlook [National Magazine], 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Sister-to-Sister, Planning Materials, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Educational Foundation Support: Branch & Member Recognition, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Educational Foundation Directory or Fellowship, Grant and Award Recipients, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Diversity Calendar, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The University Woman Texas! [State Newsletter], 1998-2002 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Food for Families [Food Drive], 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Education, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Educational Foundation Resource Guide, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Women’s Legislative Day, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Education & Equality: Choice for a Changing World, 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Outlook [National Magazine], 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Photographs and Scrapbooks, 1926-2002, undated; 4